[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 25]
How much is it?
Miss,
this bracelet is unusual.
This pearl is made of
the Lake Demon's eye.
She dug out one of her eyes for her children
and raised it in the golden clam.
It can repel demons and suppress evil spirits.
It will definitely work.
-Liar. -He made it up.
What are you talking about?
You know nothing.
Why do I think
someone will buy it?
5,000 taels.
I'll buy it.
Don't let the Lake Demon
dig out another eye
for her children in the winter.
Miss.
It's you
I've been waiting for.
You don't know me?
I...
suppose.
I remember last night
when I was pulled out of the water last night,
I seem to remember
I told someone
about the Lake Demon here.
I gave this pearl
to a girl.
That girl...
That girl is me.
My name is Liu Shao.
You are...
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
The moon rose to the tip of the willow.
Good name.
You...
What did you call me?
Luo Ge.
♫This is a spring song♫
You forgot everything.
♫The peach blossoms fly with the swallow♫
How can you break the Soul-devouring Spell?
I really can't remember that.
♫Whose lights are light and shine people's way home?♫
I think I saw it when I was floating.
I remember
I owe it to someone.
♫The clouds roll the sunset♫
So...
So I grabbed it.
♫The moon kisses the eyebrows♫
♫I am waiting for you to say♫
♫Tonight in this life♫
Sorry.
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
I broke
the treasure Lu Li left you.
♫I miss you so much♫
No.
♫I still remember the youth♫
What's wrong?
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
This...
I owe you this?
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
I'm sorry.
Here...
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
This...
This is for you.
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
And this too.
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
Take these.
♫Send you to the Western State♫
It's all yours.
Don't cry, okay?
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
I don't want these.
I only want you.
You want me?
It's okay.
But actually...
I'm
not that expensive.
I'm not worth 5,000 taels.
1,000 taels will do.
No.
One copper coin will do.
Lu Li sold himself to Liu Shao
with one copper coin.
Will you regret it?
Never.
Lu Li, you liar!
Have you forgotten?
I gave you one copper coin.
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
Why do you break your promise?
♫I miss you so much♫
You can't cheat.
♫I still remember the youth♫
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
Go back to the mortal world
and break the Soul-devouring Spell?
I don't even remember these words.
Now,
you're just getting through the tribulation in the mortal world.
After this,
you will still be an immortal.
Everyone will respect you.
Everyone will respect me.
It doesn't sound happy.
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
I don't remember the past.
♫Send you to the Western State♫
Now,
I'm just an ordinary
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
mortal person.
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
Liu Shao.
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
I don't know why
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
I
don't want
the immortal life you mentioned.
The peace and happiness
makes me feel at ease.
Liu Shao.
It's good to be like this.
Stay with me in the mortal world.
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
Because of your Sun Fragments,
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
Ge is in great pain.
The person you love is suffering because of you.
♫Send you to the Western State♫
Don't you feel sad?
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
It was me
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
who hurt you.
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
Liu Shao,
I have to face my responsibility
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫.
and get through the tribulation again.
That's impossible.
We are destined not to be together.
Instead of fighting for what we want so desperately,
we might as well let go.
I'll take you to a place.
See for yourself how the Three Realms
need you.
I'll go help them.
This...
What should I do?
Well...
Should I do something?
It seems to be
like this.
It's useless.
Let me try again.
Brother.
Help...
Help me.
Do something
and send them away.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Liu Shao.
My sister-in-law is really amazing.
Brother.
You...
I remember
that's how it works.
Didn't sister-in-law say you went missing?
Why are you here?
You told me yesterday that you wanted to kill demons here.
I found him
and brought him here.
Sister-in-law.
Liu Shao.
I saw you defeated them.
Are you okay?
Sister-in-law.
What's wrong with brother?
He...
He has no magic power anymore?
Something happened when Luo Ge was practicing.
He doesn't remember the past.
So
he can't do magic for now.
Who is your brother?
You.
Do you know
you almost killed me?
What?
Do you want your sister-in-law to be a widow?
Listen.
This tone
must be my brother's.
But...
What's going on?
Many people have been missing in the city these days.
Jian and I came to investigate this.
We found that some demons were killing people to get the vitality.
So we came to save people.
I didn't expect those demons are so cunning
to ambush here.
I...
I didn't help much.
Looks like
I have to learn some magic.
I wanted to protect you guys, but now,
I can only rely on you to protect me.
Brother,
you have protected many people.
The whole human world
should thank you.
Liu Shao.
Master Shang.
You found him?
Who is this?
If he doesn't go back,
I don't know.
we'll be in trouble.
-You don't know him either? -He doesn't seem to remember anything.
No.
Please
tell the immortals that
I will take Immortal Luo Ge back
to the Immortal Palace safely.
Liu Shao,
who is this pretty?
He looks quite gentle.
But he's wearing too much make-up.
Luo Ge,
look at you.
You're still so mean.
Look carefully.
I was born beautiful.
I don't wear makeup.
Master Shang,
are you here to catch up with us?
No.
I have something important
to ask you.
Please come with me.
Liu Shao.
What?
The evil spirit of the Four Seasons Monument is emitting again?
Yes.
Luo Ge is not here.
Only your Blood Amulet can
hold back these evil things.
I know.
How many are you going to take?
I will take one first.
It will work for three days.
I hope you can
help him
get him through the tribulation in three days.
Otherwise...
Liu Shao.
I know this is unfair to you.
If I had other ways,
I wouldn't have come to you.
Without Luo Ge,
can the talisman pearl suppress it?
A talisman pearl
can only last three more days for the Three Realms.
Just wait and see.
If Luo Ge doesn't come back
in three days,
the Four Seasons Monument will be completely out of control.
The Three Realms will be in chaos.
Take one first.
I'll try to help Luo Ge recall the past.
We can only rely on you
for the next three days.
Sorry.
Liu Shao.
Where are you?
Master Shang.
Please
cast a Silence Spell on me.
I'm afraid
I'll scream in pain.
He will be sad
when he hears my voice.
Okay.
This will be the fifth talisman pearl from you.
It will hurt your vitality.
You'd better
take good care of yourself after this.
Don't worry.
Liu Shao.
I can't even protect Liu Shao
with no magic power.
Is this the feeling?
Liu Shao.
What's wrong?
Why are you so weak?
Where have you been?
I’m fine.
I just talked to Master Shang
and fell down.
You fell?
Did you hurt yourself?
No.
Can you
carry me for a while?
Okay.
Did Luo Ge do anything to you?
He probably wants to kill me.
But
he has no power now.
There is nothing he can do.
You are showing off.
He will make you pay for this.
Seal it now.
Okay.
That pretty.
Isn't he asking for death?
My sister-in-law hurt so bad
after he took her out for a while.
Exactly.
Immortal Luo Ge.
When you regain your power,
you have to peel him.
Yes.
Hang him on the wall
for three days.
Yes.
I will.
I said it was me.
Greetings, Senior Lu.
Greetings, Immortal Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
They are...
They are thanking you
for saving the mortal world.
Thank me?
The Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
was occupied by the Demon Realm.
The mortal world almost became a part of the Demon Realm.
You rebuilt
the Marquis Wuyang's Mansion by yourself
and gave the elites of the mortal world a place to recuperate
and rebuilt the order of the mortal world.
Yes.
My brother is the hero of the Three Realms,
the guardian of the Three Realms.
Get up.
Do you remember anything?
No.
I'm just thinking
how a couple
live in the mortal world?
Wang Jian,
how did you
live?
Just like that.
You build a few huts,
do some farm work,
and raise a few ducks. Is it hard?
No, no.
That's good.
Luo Ge.
When will you remember who you are?
I made a promise with the Immortal before.
After I subdue the Four Demons,
the Immortal will return Fu to me.
Now the Four Demons have been subdued
and have made me the king.
Please keep your promise.
Immortal is getting through the tribulation.
We can't decide
what he promised.
The thunder stroke
and the Xiyin Mountain is descending.
Is Immortal really getting through the tribulation?
He Na.
This is the Immortal Palace's business.
You crossed the line.
The Three Realms are related as a whole.
If there is any change in the Immortal Palace,
the Demons will be affected.
Fine.
The Immortal Palace will keep our promises.
Follow me.
He's not Fu.
We wanted to
free Fu back to the Demon Realm.
But he escaped.
This is different.
It belongs to Luo Ning.
Could it be that
she was abducted by your brother too?
It belongs to Fairy Luo Ning.
Don't worry.
I'll find Fu and ask him
and give you an explanation.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Brother, sister-in-law.
Brother.
Chicken.
Rabbits.
Pomegranate tree
and peach blossoms.
Brother,
what you want
is like this, right?
Do you like it?
I've never lived in a place like this.
And I've never raised chicken and ducks.
But
I like it.
That's good.
Brother, sister-in-law,
you can stay here in peace from now on.
Xue,
let's cook some delicious dishes
to welcome them tonight.
No problem.
Let's go.
Slow down.
What should we cook?
Pick the vegetables.
How are you?
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
It's just that...
you still have a lot of responsibilities.
Luo Ge.
You're an immortal.
I'm a mortal.
I can't do magic.
Even if I can,
I will protect
the person I care about.
The Three Realms are too much.
I can't bear it.
Let's go.
Help them cook.
You see how cute
these two goats are.
Hurry up.
Keep up.
Is this the important thing you mentioned?
You've been weak lately.
When they grow up,
they can produce milk for you.
Let's live our life
in the yard.
I will plant some vegetables.
By then,
I'll plow the soil in the yard
and plant some vegetables.
The vegetables
must be very delicious.
Let's go.
You seem to remember what Lu Li promised me.
But if you can't remember Luo Ge's past,
how can you break the Soul-Devouring Spell?
I wonder where my brother is.
The mortal world is so big.
I don't know where to find him.
Immortal Luo Ge is blessed by God.
He will be happy
that you care about him.
Come on.
What do you like?
Take a look.
What do you want to buy?
Are you okay, Fu?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Fu.
Look over there.
Let's go.
Go.
Go!
Miss! Miss!
Take mine.
My fan is good.
Mine is good.
Look at mine.
Miss.
I know the custom of your Dusting Festival.
Giving a fan
to express your love, right?
Unfortunately,
I'm only interested in
your hearts.
Fu.
Look.
There are many beautiful fans here.
Choose one and give it to me.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll buy it for you.
You can buy whatever you want,
as long as you don't accept theirs.
Do you think I'll take things from anyone?
Take a look.
Okay.
This fan is beautiful.
Which one do you want?
So beautiful.
Do you like it?
Fu,
look.
Welcome.
Have a look.
Fu.
If I wear this,
no one will come to give me a fan.
Well,
I'll choose this one.
If someone dares to give you a fan,
I can scare them away
like this.
Fu,
You look ugly in this.
Let me see you.
Look.
My little fairy is pretty.
I will take these two.
Thank you.
Fu,
let's go there.
Let's go.
Thank you.
There are people
who chose Demon King and Immortal Ze Shui's masks
these days.
I will go to the mortal world myself.
Also,
no one can know
about Fu's escape.
I'm afraid something will happen.
Yes.
Fu,
I spoiled you too much
and let you cause troubles
every time.
What would you do
if the Immortal Palace intervenes in it?
[Qianyuan Tea House]
Guests,
here is the water. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Drink it.
It smells so good.
You want to eat almond cake?
I have never tried it.
I'll buy it for you.
Okay.
[Fortune-telling]
Miss,
do you need a fortune teller?
No.
Then...
Are you looking for...
Are you looking for someone?
You know this?
Just focus on the compass
and think about the person you are looking for.
This compass
will show you
the direction of the person.
[Qianyuan Tea House]
[Fortune-telling]
I've been looking for so long.
I finally found a person with spiritual power.
After I take the vitality out of her,
I believe
Master will be very happy.
How dare you hurt her?
Do you want to die?
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning, how are you?
Fu.
It hurts.
Where?
Luo Ning.
Watch out!
Brother.
People died after being taken off the vitality
in the mortal world recently.
It seems that
the collapse of the market is because of you guys.
Tell me.
Who asked you
to collect the vitality everywhere?
Demon King.
I...
It's evil spirit again.
Could it be the Luo Ge
in the Four Seasons Monument?
The Four Seasons Monument is getting more dangerous.
Fu.
Brother.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Luo Ning.
This is...
It's fine.
Don't move.
Fairy.
Fu,
go back to the Demon Palace
and leave Fairy to me.
I'll take her back to the Immortal Palace.
No way.
Fu.
She's Luo Ge's sister.
She's not someone you can bring out.
Are you afraid of offending the Immortal Palace?
The Immortal Palace is in turmoil.
The Three Realms are in turmoil.
Stop causing trouble.
But it's Fairy Luo Ning.
I won't let her go.
Besides, she has helped the Aquatic Demons.
I want to keep her.
Fu!
Fu.
So...
So Fairy Luo Ning
is really the heir of Immortal Ze Shui.
Here, take your medicine.
Fu.
That demon
devoured half of my vitality.
Ordinary medicine
can't save me.
I've thought about it.
Send me back to the Immortal Palace as soon as possible.
I'm afraid...
if something happens to me,
you will be implicated.
I'm not afraid of the Immortal Palace. I...
I mean
I brought you here.
I will cure you.
No.
I insisted on looking for my brother.
It has nothing to do with you.
As long as I can find my brother...
But...
I don't know where my brother is now.
I'm afraid we can't find him
for a while.
Don't think about your brother.
Take care of yourself.
I'm here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Fu.
Your vitality is damaged.
You just need to
make up for the damaged vitality.
Don't worry.
Fu.
Long time no see.
It's you.
God of the Moonlight.
I didn't expect you to be able to convey messages with your mind.
I have to
thank
the fairy with you.
Thanks to the half of her vitality,
it's more nutritious than thousands of the mortals.
It's really you.
I'm warning you.
Don't hurt Luo Ning again.
Also,
when you regain your power,
don't forget your promise.
Brat,
I will let you know
the difference between the king and the subordinate.
Good boy.
You feed the rabbits and goats
before breakfast?
I also checked
whether the seeds sprout.
Time passes so slowly.
It's only been two days.
It's been three days.
Three days.
On the first day we met,
we rowed at Moon River
and then went to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
You took me to the Moon Washing Pond yesterday.
What about today?
Where will we go today?
Wherever you want to go.
Do you remember anything these days?
Liu Shao.
I know you're trying
to remind me of the past.
But I've thought about it.
From the first day I came here,
I felt like I was looking for something.
But
I knew I found it from the moment I saw you.
I don't want to
be some immortal.
I just want to live with you like this.
Anything else?
Well,
Wang Jian wants to improve his skills.
He wants me to help him.
I have an idea
to realize all of these
within one day.
Tell me.
Let go of your obsession
and become the Immortal.
The Three Realms
will be under your control.
If I want to regain my memory, I need to return to the Immortal Palace.
What about you?
Where would you be?
You always want me to find my past.
But what I want
is you.
I don't want to get through
the tribulation.
If you don't want to face it,
then wait for three more days.
Make your decision
after three days.
Let alone three days,
even if it's three or thirty years,
I'll have the same answer.
I don't want to be Immortal Luo Ge.
I just want to be a mortal.
But I don't have that much time left.
Luo Ge.
Three days.
Just three days.
What if I disappear one day
and you can't find me?
Don't you dare.
Try me.
Sorry.
Luo Ge.
If you still can't remember,
let me help you fulfill your responsibilities.
It's just three days
and the talisman pearl couldn't stop it.
Even the formation is weakening.
We don't have the eye of formation.
The eye of formation?
The location of Liu Shao
is the eye of formation.
Although Liu Shao is not powerful,
she has the power of the Sun Spirit.
So she can suppress the formation.
Besides, this formation
was set by Luo Ge.
Even without the eye of formation,
it's more powerful than my formation.
Now the formation has been corroded by evil spirit.
If anything happens to
the person who guards the eye of formation,
the person will be devoured by evil spirit.
I will go.
The Immortal Palace
should be led by you young people.
Immortal Master is highly respected.
You'd better take charge of the situation here.
I've been enjoying the undeserved reputation of the head of the Palaces
for a long time.
I'm your senior.
It's not your turn to be the eye of formation.
Go and see Luo Ge.
This tribulation
is not only about him.
He must get through it.
Okay.
If he can't get through this tribulation,
you must take the sixth talisman pearl back.
But after taking the sixth talisman pearl,
I'm afraid Liu Shao will be...
I'll take the Ancient Herb and Glazed Fruit
to her.
Master Zhuo.
We're counting on you.